<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EcclesiaV2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="qr_scanner_text">Place QR code in scanner box</string>
    <string name="stateInfoTxt">\u25CF Joined election: When you have joined the election.
        \n\u25CF Voting started: Voting period has begun. You can now begin to cast your vote.
        \n\u25CF Vote casted: You have casted your vote.
        \n\u25CF Vote recorded: Your vote has been recorded to the blockchain and can be guaranteed to be counted in the final result.
        \n\u25CF Results calculated: The final result has been calculated. </string>
    <string name="statusOneDescription">Others are still joining the election, you can join the election at DD/MM/YY HH:MM.</string>
    <string name="statusTwoDescription">You can now begin voting.</string>
    <string name="statusThreeDescription">Your vote has been casted and is in the process of being recorded to the blockchain.</string>
    <string name="statusFourTrueDescription">Your vote has been recorded onto the blockchain. All the votes will be calculated after the voting ends.</string>
    <string name="statusFourFalseDescription">Your vote could not be recorded to the blockchain. Find out how to resolve this issue.</string>
    <string name="confirmationDialogBold">Are you sure you want to cast this vote?</string>
    <string name="confirmationDialogNormal">Once you cast a vote, you will not be able to change your vote.</string>
    <string name="castedTxt3">You vote has been encrypted and casted. It will take some time for it to be recorded to the blockchain.</string>
    <string name="castedTxt4">Come back later to verify it has been recorded successfully.</string>
    <string name="organisationInstruction">Scan an organisations QR code to eligible for their future elections.</string>
    <string name="electionInstruction">Scan an elections QR code to join and be able to vote.</string>
    <string name="learnMore">Learn more</string>
    <string name="learnToFix">Learn how to fix this issue</string>

        <string name="ecclesiaDifferentQ">What makes E-cclesia different/better than other voting systems?</string>
        <string name="ecclesiaDifferentA">E-cclesia is the only currently available fully decentralised voting system. For a voting system to be decentralised, this means that everyone involved in the election can take part in counting the votes. This is more secure than centralised voting systems that depend on one party to count all the votes because it is secure against corruption and counting errors. E-cclesia also satisfies more security properties than other available voting systems. </string>
<!--        <string name="ecclesiaPropertiesQ">What security properties does E-cclesia satisfy? </string>-->
<!--        <string name="ecclesiaPropertiesA">\u25CF Correctness: Every honestly cast vote will be counted in the final tally and this result is the same for all parties involved as long as no tampering has occurred.-->
<!--            \n\u25CF Eligibility: Only eligible voters will be able to vote.-->
<!--            \n\u25CF Fairness: No partial result can be learned while the voting period is open. until everyone has cast their vote.-->
<!--            \n\u25CF Voter privacy: Voter's identities cannot be linked to their vote.-->
<!--            \n\u25CF One voter one vote: Only one vote from every eligible voter will be counted in the final tally.-->
<!--            \n\u25CF Verifiability: Any party can be certain that that their vote has been recorded and that all recorded all votes have been counted in the final tally. </string>-->
        <string name="ecclesiaStepsQ">What are the steps involved in the E-cclesia voting system for a voter?</string>
        <string name="ecclesiaStepsA">1. Register to the organisations’ electoral roll which will be used in the set up of their elections.that sets up the elections on E-cclesia. The registration invite will be sent through email.
            \n2. Joined the election that will take place on E-cclesia. The joining invite will be sent through email.
            \n3. Cast your vote.
            \n4. Verify that your vote has been recorded. If it has not, you will be able to recast your vote and notify us that this issue occurred.
            \n5. View the final results of the election. </string>
        <string name="ecclesiaStatesQ">What are the different states of an election? </string>
        <string name="ecclesiaStatesA">1. Joined election: When you have joined the election.
            \n2. Voting started: Voting period has begun. You can now begin to cast your vote.
            \n3. Vote casted: You have casted your vote.
            \n4. Vote recorded: Your vote has been recorded to the blockchain and can be guaranteed to be counted in the final result.
            \n5. Results calculated: The final result has been calculated. </string>
        <string name="whyRegisteredQ">Why do I have to be registered to an organisation to join in an election? </string>
        <string name="whyRegisteredA">To ensure that only eligible voters can vote in a specific election, the app needs tosystem generates unique encrypted credentials for these voterseach voter. These credentials can only be generated and stored once a user has registered with the organisation. </string>
        <string name="abstainQ">Can I abstain from voting? </string>
        <string name="abstainA">Yes. If you have already registered for the election and not cast a vote, you can still see the results without voting.</string>
        <string name="joinAfterQ">Can I join elections after the vote casting period has started? </string>
        <string name="joinAfterA">No. To satisfy the security properties of E-cclesia, only people who have joined the election before the casting period starts can cast a vote. </string>
        <string name="voteAgainQ">Can I vote again?</string>
        <string name="voteAgainA">No. As your vote will begin the process of being recorded to the blockchain once you have casted your vote, it is not possible to recast a vote. </string>
        <string name="howLongQ">How long does it take to verify that my vote has been recorded?</string>
        <string name="howLongA">There is no average time for this process, but there are estimated lower boundaries and upper boundaries. Usually, this process can take anywhere between 5 minutes and 4 hours.</string>
        <string name="howVerifyQ">How do I verify that my vote has been recorded?</string>
        <string name="howVerifyA">When you open the election you voted for, the application will automatically run the required steps to verify this behind the scenes. There is nothing voters need to do manually other than checking the app frequently after casting their vote so you can check the result of the verification. It is important to verify that your vote has been recorded on the chance that it has not been recorded. There are no extra steps you required other than need to take to verify this. </string>
        <string name="ifVoteProblemQ">What happens if my vote has not been recorded? </string>
        <string name="ifVoteProblemA">On the chance that your vote could not be verified as recorded, then you are allowed to recast your vote. This will be immediately detected by the application, and you should be able to recast your vote as long as the casting period has not ended yet. You are also highly recommended to report this error to us to record the number of similar errors occurred and take action. </string>
    <string name="whyVoteProblemQ">Why would my vote not be recorded? </string>
    <string name="whyVoteProblemA">Once a vote has been casted it is stored on a server before being sent to be recorded to the blockchain at which point it is guaranteed to be part of the final result of votes for the election. Occasionally a communication error or malicious  attack between the application to the server or the server to the blockchain can occur, preventing this from happening. </string>
    <string name="solveProblem">To overcome this issue, please email <u>s1908227@ed.ac.uk</u> to let us know that this issue occurred and vote again. </string>
</resources>