<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EcclesiaV2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="qr_scanner_text">Place QR code in scanner box</string>
    <string name="stateInfoTxt">\u25CF Joined election: When you have joined the election.
        \n\u25CF Voting started: Voting period has begun. You can now begin to cast your vote.
        \n\u25CF Vote casted: You have casted your vote.
        \n\u25CF Vote recorded: Your vote has been recorded to the blockchain and can be guaranteed to be counted in the final result.
        \n\u25CF Results calculated: The final result has been calculated. </string>
    <string name="statusOneDescription">Others are still joining the election, you can join the election at DD/MM/YY HH:MM.</string>
    <string name="statusTwoDescription">You can now begin voting.</string>
    <string name="statusThreeDescription">Your vote has been casted and is in the process of being recorded to the blockchain.</string>
    <string name="statusFourTrueDescription">Your vote has been recorded onto the blockchain. All the votes will be calculated after the voting ends.</string>
    <string name="statusFourFalseDescription">Your vote could not be recorded to the blockchain. Find out how to resolve this issue.</string>
    <string name="confirmationDialogBold">Are you sure you want to cast this vote?</string>
    <string name="confirmationDialogNormal">Once you cast a vote, you will not be able to change your vote.</string>
    <string name="castedTxt3">You vote has been encrypted and casted. It will take some time for it to be recorded to the blockchain.</string>
    <string name="castedTxt4">Come back later to verify it has been recorded successfully.</string>
    <string name="organisationInstruction">Scan an organisations QR code to eligible for their future elections.</string>
    <string name="electionInstruction">Scan an elections QR code to join and be able to vote.</string>
    <string name="learnMore"><u>Learn more</u></string>
</resources>